Crypto is dead, man.
It's over. It's not the same. Um, as you
guys know, I've been in crypto since
2015.
And I can take it from me. This is
the most boring I have ever seen crypto.
Um, the most discouraging.
Um, nobody's building anything.
Um, and
you know, over the past, man, 10 years,
I can officially say I've been in crypto
for 10 years because I came in at the
end of 2015.
It's 2026 now. So after 10 years of
everything I've learned,
I took all that knowledge
and I told some developers to build
something. I ain't do it.
Told the developers to build something.
um all of the flywheels that failed,
all of the mechanisms,
and we'll get into crypto as a whole.
Bitcoin is
now at 88K. ETH's back under 3,000.
Um gold and metals are going up to new
highs every day. We'll talk about that.
But first,
I want to
get into less.
So, like I said,
I've seen it all.
I see where everybody messed up. I think
it's the perfect time. It's kind of
lining up beautifully, actually, because
nobody's building anything. All the
building stopped. All the Huh. Let's try
this. Well, what if we did this? All
that has stopped and it seems like I'm
the only one left.
Um,
so I kept Well, I ain't build any nut,
but
I
orchestrated. I don't like that one
either. I ain't do nothing. I ain't That
ain't got nothing to do with this
really.
Nah. Um, yeah, I built something, man.
And, um, allegedly and, um, it's coming
out on the 26th. Now, I remember I
promised that I would never build
another cryptocurrency
unless it helped out more.
Um,
so
I think the test net's going to come out
today.
Um, go to my Twitter.
Don't think there's going to be a white
paper.
Um, it'll kind of I kind of like the
idea of just letting it go and letting
it be free and not hyping it up.
I like the idea of a little bit coming
in here and there because the way it's
built,
you know, it's got, you know, the way
it's built, it doesn't need to be. I
mean, of course, it would be great if it
was hyped up because it would feel it
would fill up
really, really fast and there would be a
lot in it. But
we know what happens. You know, people
FOMO and things go down
and
the fingers start pointing.
So, I would much rather this be
something that just kind of goes
organic.
Um,
so essentially what it is is, uh,
it's a mining
flywheel.
You heard that,
man. The universe is crazy, man. Um,
so it's a mining flywheel. Now, what
happened is everyone got it right. All
the developers got it right with the buy
and burn. The most genius thing ever
implemented.
But the problem with every buy and burn,
either it's centralized or has admin
keys that can change it
or it goes to the wrong people or it
goes it comes in and is used at the
wrong time. Typically way too early.
every buy and burn I've seen, even if
they did something that they kind of,
you know, they kind of delay it and um
make it a a
type of um pump fund or something like
that where funds start getting deployed
later.
They do it. It's too early. It's still
like in this phase where there's still
dumping going on like um you can see
with Titan X
um Blaze
um
D well DBZ didn't have a buying burn.
So, you know, I took parts of
allegedly I took parts of everything
that
I enjoyed the past 10 years and I put it
in a ball
and said, "Can you build this?"
Hell yeah.
Just Just
done. That took a while though. a lot of
tweaking.
Um, but I'm excited about it because
it's not gonna be hyped up. It's gonna
be just like something you know, you
know. Um, so you mine it and
you know, the purpose of it is to just
get the ETH out. Let's be real. Let's be
real. The purpose is to extract the ETH
out of it. But the only way to extract
the ETH out of it is you got to have
some less, you know, or you got to try
and get some less.
So there's no way to get the ETH out
other than participating
in some type of, you know, fashion. So
the objective is to get the ETH out of
it. And the objective of the protocol is
to keep the ETH for as long as possible.
So yeah, I'm excited, man. It comes out
on the 26th. That's this Monday, 10:00
a.m. I think allegedly. Don't go buy
anything. Don't go do anything because
of this. It's just we're just
experimenting, social experiments. I
mean, for real, like that's that's no
there's no undertone there. This is
literally what this is to see if
something will work. Um,
and uh, yeah, Monday it should go live
at 10:00 a.m.
I'll try to be live on a live stream. If
not, then I didn't really talk about it
anyway.
But yeah, Bitcoin Bitcoin's looking uh,
pretty
it's not looking good. I I must say that
it's not looking good. Now, I've been
You guys been wondering where my videos
are. I've been doing videos this entire
time for members. So, click the join
button down below. Yeah, I'm going to be
that guy right now. Sorry. Click the
join button down below to become a
member.
Um, and I'm been pretty accurate. I I
don't really remember, but I know that I
was bearish up here when when ETH was
pumping. I got Twitter post on there
when I was selling ETH. You can go find
it. It's not far. It wasn't long ago. I
retweeted it and pinned it. I should pin
it. So people are like, "Where was she
at?" I called the top. I just didn't say
this is the top, but I kind of made a
did a action. I wish I would have sold
more for sure. Um it was when it was
like 40. It was like back here maybe. I
can't really remember which one it was,
but it was pushing 49. I I almost sold
everything. I wish I would have though.
But anyway, so we were looking good the
other day.
Um
we need a to recover this move. I don't
want to be doing charts, guys. I mean, I
know some of you guys want to see this.
So, here it is. Here are my thoughts on
where I think we're going. Um, but yo,
to be real, that's why I need to fix
this cuz
to be real,
doesn't really matter, man. Just hold on
to the crypto. Increase your units.
That's my new thing I've been saying.
Increase your units. So, if you have,
you know, for Salana Bros., If you have
one Salana, try and get 1.1, work your
way up to 1.2 and then get your way up
to two and three. Like, if you treat
crypto like that, I must say that is
actually has been the the secret that
really worked if you did it with the
right things, which it wasn't hard to do
it with the right things as long as you
weren't being greedy. Because I think a
lot of people are like really focused
on,
well, that one's already gone up, so
what's the next thing I want to be in
the thing that's cheaper that's going to
go up when really all that time and
money spent buying those coins could
have just went into Bitcoin. It's like
gh it hurts to say that [__] but yeah,
they were right. and ETH and Salana B&B.
But if you just stuck with the winners,
I think that's the key. Just stick with
the winners, man. Don't try and I mean,
yeah, you can try, but I'm not going to
stop you from trying, but I would
recommend
having the mindset it's not too late.
It's actually it's actually still pretty
early if you look in the grand scheme of
things like 21 million Bitcoin, 100
million ETH, you know,
it's not much of it, man. And it's going
to get lo like if you This is time, man.
Time is flying by a lot faster. I don't
know if it's just me. I'm pretty sure
it's you guys, too, where you're getting
older, so time is speeding up. So, your
time horizons need to be longer. And
don't worry about the the how long it's
going to take because you're going to
outpace everybody anyway because people
can't do it. You think you're behind,
but you're not behind when you go on the
street. When you go on the streets, do
you see many We'll just go off cars,
man. Because cars say a lot about a
person. Do you see many cars that look
like they really going to get far? And
most cars you see it's like they stop.
It's easy to pass get past that level,
man. It's just don't do what they're
doing and they're spending money on dumb
[__] buying dumb [__] wasting it on
this, wasting it on that. Just keep it
and put it in stuff. It's really as
simple as that. Just keep it.
Put it in
say anything. Anything that's working.
Gold, silver, Bitcoin, Salana. Sh. I've
been thinking about copper. Copper,
that's my next play. I might start
talking about that [__] Sports cards,
Pokemon, Magic.
Put it in any of that stuff because when
you buying it, it's not like when you
buy food or something to drink. When you
buy food, that's like the biggest waste
of money you can actually have because
when you eat it, the only thing you got
is some satisfaction.
That's deep. Actually, it's deep as
[__] It's deep as [__] You only get
satisfaction. So, at least when you buy
an an object, you can sell it. You can
sell it. And it's really easy to sell
stuff nowadays. Just put it cheaper than
everybody else's. Like, if I want to
sell this phone, I can sell it. I mean,
I wouldn't do that. I can trade it in,
but you get what I'm saying. um
you know as long as you're buying right
which is like now depends but something
like Bitcoin maybe get some now
ETH Salana get some now man it's down it
might go down some more but I don't
think that Bitcoin is going to go much
lower than
70,000
now 70,000 is is my magic number right
now because that is the there's this new
thing that I found outside of the stock
toflow
which right now it's the stock too but
there's this new thing I found I can't
find a chart for it but I see it every
now and then that kind of keeps me
updated the mining the production cost
of one bitcoin is around 70,000 and
there's a chart out there somebody in
the comments Maybe you can tell me what
it is so I can look it up. I don't know.
Maybe I could look Bitcoin production
cost or something like that. But the
price never goes below that. And if it
does, it doesn't stay there for more
than maybe a couple days. So, and that
number right now is like 71. Now, I know
a lot of people are probably going to be
looking for much cheaper, but I think
that is the secret is it's not going
below that number. So,
you know,
yeah, maybe get start buying. We're
turning green on the stock to PO. Now,
this has been pretty invalid since uh I
think it broke on the well, it didn't it
broke on this cycle as far as the stock
to flow, but the price end of day, this
right here, days until next having is
still spot on.
as of now when it starts to turn orange.
And this is what I was saying the whole
time we was in this red and orange. I
really recommend going back and watching
the videos from back here and when I
when I would bring this I was in some
[__] too. I was playing around doing
my [__] But as far as the grand
scheme of things, this has been spot on
every single time. Orange to yellow. We
gonna say orange to yellow. Cell to a
fellow.
Orange to yellow. Cell to a fellow.
Yellow to green.
We have to think of something.
But yeah,
this is starting to turn green. Now what
I think
the most likely thing is we just we we
chop around. I don't think we get that
crash like maybe we do.
That would suck. But I think what people
aren't expecting is just chopping around
here
while it's green that this is might not
have been the bottom, but pretty close.
Maybe we get down to that 70, but I
mean, if we go down to 70, it's not
really that much lower than this low
back here. So, I don't think we could
be, but I don't that would suck. But I
don't see that. I don't see us going all
the way down here
before
the having. Like we should be about
there now. Let's see. Well, I mean, we
could cuz we're like right here.
Everybody's Now, that's another thing,
too, is everybody's looking down. That's
another thing I've been saying is when
people are looking down,
it's probably going up. So, I'm starting
to look down.
So, I think we go up from here. We
already kind of recovering it.
And I think, you know, once we get back
to 90
inside these moving averages,
you know, but that [__] like I was
saying, it doesn't it's all a
distraction. This right here when I go
into it's a distraction, man. You can
look at you can just you could literally
just look at the stock the flowchart,
Bitcoin production cost, and it'll tell
you what the where the market's going.
You can literally just do that. But
every time people will be like, "Oh, no.
This time is different. This time it's
going to be different but it this stock
toflow has never Bitcoin production cost
and stock to flow has yet to be
invalidated.
So
I don't think that I I hope I'm wrong
but I don't think that we're going back
up to a new high. I think we're more
likely to just chop around here until
the next having between 70 and 90. And
then the next having comes and that's
when
it starts to get good again. Like
so now's the time to be accumulating in
my opinion.
Um,
if I had gold and silver,
if I really was like a gold bug and a
silver bug
back, you know, when I should have been
I mean, I was buying was what's funny is
I actually been buying silver allegedly.
Started like 25 or something like that.
Maybe it seemed like it was lower than
that, but I mean higher than that, but I
think it was around 25.
and I I put it on an auto subscription
and now I'm like, huh, I should sell all
my silver for gold, but it's like, damn,
gold is up, too. So, what's the play? If
I was a silver bug, it' probably be the
hard thing to do would be sell that for
Bitcoin. I mean, that's probably the
hard one of the hardest trades to make
because it's like the complete opposite
of what your mentality is like. Metals
are real physical, you know? And I think
that's the trade is and it's an obvious
one
which is kind of scary because usually
the obvious stuff doesn't really play
out but I mean look at this silver chart
guys.
It's parabolic.
You know it's due to clean up and head
to this 200. I think that's around 50.
You know, by the time it plays out, I
think silver is going to be like 50.
It's going to settle out like that's a
round that's a nice round number. And
you know, gold
cuz think about it, they think gold is
about to break 5,000, silver is about to
break 100. Duh. Right? That's what a a
dummy would say. I think like I watch
silver videos and
stuff like that and they're like, "Well,
we're going past when we get past 100."
They're doing the same [__] Bitcoiners
do when they start looking up and like
guaranteeing that it's going to go to a
price. It's usually a top.
I mean, we'll be over 100 here shortly.
[__] like that. Never goes like that.
Well, it does, but it doesn't stay above
those numbers. So,
if I was in that stuff, I would rotate
to crypto.
That's what I'm thinking.
So,
um, what else?
I think copper is another play, too. I
google not I googled I well what I AIed
um
I asked AI if
um AI uses copper a lot of copper and it
said yes. It said one data center is
like 50,000 tons of copper and copper
hasn't really ran like silver and gold
has from what I've seen. I don't have a
chart on there. I don't know which chart
to look at. I guess the ounce, but I
couldn't find it. Um, but I looked this
morning. I didn't really look hard. But
I'm thinking that might be a play. The
problem with copper though is like it's
very cheap. So, you have to buy a lot
and a lot is going to take up a lot of
space. And that's why I like sports
cards because one of these can be worth,
you know, I mean, they're can be worth a
lot. like
millions, you know, if this was like a a
Mickey Manel or something, it's like a
million in it perfect condition. Million
dollars in one little piece of plastic
in a piece of cardboard. So, space
starts to become important when you
start to get mega wealthy. Not talking
about me.
This just things I think about if I were
to get like insanely rich. Where can I
store all of it? What's something small?
crypto, but what's something physical?
Cards. Um, so copper is going to take up
a lot of space. So, not really trying to
have
um
tons of I mean, ounces of copper in my
house. I mean, how much is a ton of
copper? Probably not even that much. I
mean, it's probably a lot, but it's not
like worth storing. You know what I'm
saying? So,
um, what else? Pulse Chain,
Richard Hart. I mean, I I have
completely checked out of now the X
algorithm has gotten really strange
lately because I mean, it's not strange,
but it makes sense. But if you start
focusing on something that's not crypto,
it's going to show you that thing.
So you kind of when you reply like a lot
of you guys I follow some of y'all and
y'all reply to stuff and it really
reveals kind of like what you're into.
So
that kind of like steers your algorithm.
So if you start just like go search my
Twitter page and then engage with some
of my stuff and you'll start seeing more
crypto stuff um or whatever you want to
see. And I think that has hurt crypto a
lot
which is scary is crypto was very
Twitter
um centric
as far as like information getting
around and I think that has hurt crypto
a lot.
Um
it almost seems intentional.
I don't know. I mean, you got Elon. He
bought up X. He bought up crypto.
And you know, you kind of hear about
these scary stories about how like the
mega wealthy like buy stuff to make the
price go down. I don't know how that's I
don't know how, but I've heard that
before. And that's kind of like maybe
that was the way to kill it by like just
Yeah.
Like if I if I had a coin, right, and I
wanted to kill it
and keep it from going up, all I would
have to do is buy up auto supply. It
would go up. But if I did it during the
hype,
I guess I could kill it because yeah, if
nobody's I mean, if if the demand stays
the same anyway.
So
yeah. Um,
that's weird. Something else has been on
my mind. Uh,
Postchain. Oh, yeah. So, Postchain is is
interesting because I don't see any
Postchain stuff on my feed cuz I just
don't care. I I don't like it's like
it's one of those posts where I see it
and I'm like, uh, I scroll right past
it. So, it just it's like, oh, he really
doesn't want that [__] Okay. Sorry,
bro. Sorry, man.
So,
um, I'm seeing a lot of stuff I'm into.
I'm seeing a lot of sports. I'm seeing
more card stuff than I'm seeing crypto.
So, YouTube though, it's the same way
with YouTube.
But, um,
YouTube will give it a shot. Like, it'll
show if like it'll show this video to a
lot of people. It'll keep on cuz I'm
it's people. I got subscribers. So yeah,
anyway,
just [__] that's been on my mind.
Postchain. See, I can't even talk about
Postchain.
It's like I try to talk about Postchain
like, "Oh yeah, they want to hear about
Postchain." Um, Postchain, it was I
mean, I don't want to say it was a scam,
but it's like
the sooner you kind of accept that [__]
like I've been accepted that [__] It's
like, eh, I didn't put everything. Like,
I think it's more about the people that
I think the people that put a lot in
that [__] that kept on buying it.
Yeah, you're wrecked.
But you got to just know when to stop
buying, man. That's another thing. Know
when to stop buying. Well, know when
it's like, all right, this it's hard to
do, man. Especially when you're having
fun. But you got to know when to stop
buying. Uh, and I never bought more
um
pulse. I mean, every I might throw a
little bit, but
like people I'm buying more that type of
money. Nah,
it's got to prove more um with me. And I
know people like you going to launch it
on postchain. Uh,
I could see it being on postchain, but
it's like, might as well, right? So,
it depends on how it does on more. I
mean, does on ETH. Yeah, that too. Um,
so the 26th,
um,
more tokens.com. There's a button at the
top that says less. You can click it
now.
more tokens.com.
Um,
and uh,
yeah, just
try not to get married to any type of
thing. Do what you like. Like I like
crypto, so I'm probably going to keep
but I'm going to buy it, right? Like I'm
I'm done
doing the dumb [__] like DCA and coins
that
are not
proving anything, you know.
Um
yeah, the things that I use. Yeah. If
I'm using crypto, I'mma buy it.
Um, I think that the space has not
really though. Like I was going to say
it has a lot of work to do, but the only
thing that needs to change is it needs
to go in to gaming.
I think that's what needs to be built on
crypto
is some type of game. You know, maybe I
should work on that next.
Build a game. But it's got to be on the
right chain.
Um, I think games like uh Arc Raiders,
you know, I don't really play much, but
I could I watch people play games,
though. Um, and I think if they made the
the endgame, like the guns and stuff
kind of like they did with um was it CS
GO? How those guns have actual real
value? Just put that [__] on the
blockchain, man.
It's like, what are you [__] waiting
on?
Uh, I think that's going to be that'll
probably be it right there.
That's what crypto needs. Or I mean,
it's happening though. Like Walmart,
they're accepting um
I think it was Walmart that started
accepting crypto payments for somebody.
And I was like, this can't be real. And
then I go, it's real.
Um,
so stuff is going on in the background
for sure, but it's like, man,
I think we just had went on a real good
run super early.
You know, you kind of would think that
crypto will be going up with it though.
Like gold, silver, Bitcoin. The fact
that it's not going up with that stuff
is what's the what's the stock market
doing? Okay, stock market is pulling
back, but it was just at new at highs at
like close to new highs. So,
yeah, it's weird. Something weird is
going on. Uh, hunker down. It's getting
kind of I would kind of scary because
it's like damn, silver, gold, Grito's
just sitting there doing nothing. Then
it also says maybe that's because it's
it's it's wait sitting and waiting on
its turn.
But usually
it don't work like that.
That turns [__]
It's like it's random.
So you just got to be positioned all the
time. I think that's the key. Just
always being being in the market.
And uh yeah, more tokens.com.
Uh
that's it.